https://mullerinsurance.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
CALL NOW: 1-201-659-2403Toggle NavigationFAQQUOTEMENUAboutOur HistoryNewsContactInsurance PoliciesFor IndividualsAutoHomeRentersCondoCo-OpLifeUmbrellaFloodDisabilityBoat, Motorcycle, RVJewelry, Fine Arts & Other CollectionsTravelDwellingOwner-Occupied DwellingTenant-Occupied DwellingFor BusinessApartment BuildingBusinessCommercial AutoWorkers’ CompensationHair Salons, Barbershops, and Nail SalonsCondo AssociationCommercial FloodBusiness UmbrellaCompaniesChubbTravelersAndoverPlymouth RockClient CenterClaimsPaymentsCertificatesCarrier ContactsResourcesFAQBlogReferral ProgramLocal Partners
You Are Here:Home/Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyGet a Quote NowPrivacy PolicyGet a Quote Now
Privacy PolicyMULLERadm2020-11-17T14:20:41-05:00
R. John Muller Insurance AgencyPrivacy Policy
Title V of the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA) generally prohibits any financial institution, directly or through its affiliates, from sharing nonpublic personal information about you with a non-affiliated third party unless the institution provides you with a notice of its privacy policies and practices, such as the type of information that it collects about you and the categories of persons or entities to whom it may be disclosed. In compliance with the GLBA, we are providing you with this document, which notifies you of the privacy policies and practices of R. John Muller Insurance Agency.
The GLBA further requires that we inform you that you have a right to prevent us from sharing nonpublic personal information about you with a non-affiliated third party for any purpose that is not specifically authorized by you, or by law. Your right to prevent us from sharing nonpublic personal information about you with a non-affiliated third party for a purpose that is not specifically authorized by you, or by law, is called your right to “opt out” of such information sharing.
OUR PRIVACY POLICIES AND PRACTICES
1. Information we collect:
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
Information we receive from you on applications or other forms.
Information about your transactions with us.
Information from search agencies.
Unless it is specifically stated otherwise in an amended Privacy Policy Notice, no additional information will be collected about you.
2. Information we may disclose to third parties:
We may disclose all of the information that we collect about you, as described above.
3. Non-affiliated third parties to whom disclosures may be made:
We may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to the following types of third parties, unless you tell us not to:
Insurance Companies, Companies through which we market your account including, insurance brokers, insurance agents, general agents, wholesale brokers and surplus lines brokers.
Realtors
Mortgage bankers and/or brokers.
Legal Professionals
Accountants
Financing Companies
Search Companies
Claim Adjusters and/or investigators
Governmental Entities
Persons to whom a Court requires us, by Order or Subpoena, to provide information.
We may also disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law.
We make every attempt not to disclose any personal information, which is not necessary for the marketing, placement and/or servicing of your account. However, if you prefer that we not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to non-affiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, that is you may direct us not to make those disclosures, by contacting our office at 201-659-2403.
4. Our practices regarding information confidentiality and security:
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
5. Our policy regarding dispute resolution:
Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to our privacy policy, or the breach thereof, shall be settled by arbitration in accordance with the rules of the American Arbitration Association, and judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitrator(s) may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof.
6. Reservation of the right to disclose information in unforeseen circumstances:
In connection with the potential sale or transfer of its interests, R. John Muller Insurance Agency reserves the right to sell or transfer your information (including but not limited to your address, name, age, sex, zip code, state and country of residency and information that you provide through other communications) to a third party entity that (1) concentrates its business in a similar practice or service; (2) agrees to be R. John Muller Insurance Agency’s successor in interest with regard to the maintenance and protection of the information collected; and (3) agrees to the obligations of this privacy statement.
Copyrights, disclosures and disclaimers
States where we do business
The product and services information included in this Web site is intended for residents of the state of New Jersey only, and is neither an offer to sell insurance nor an advertisement of insurance in any place except the state of New Jersey. R. John Muller is licensed to sell insurance in the following states: New Jersey, New York, Connecticut, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.
Authorization of use
R. John Muller hereby authorizes any person to access this Web site for informational purposes only. R. John Muller reserves the right to terminate access to this Web site at any time without notice. The data, information and material included in this Web site is copyrighted by R. John Muller. All rights are reserved under the copyright laws of the United State of America. No part of this Web site can be redistributed, copied or reproduced without the prior written consent of R. John Muller.
No warranties
The user of this Web site assumes all responsibility and risk for the use of this Web site and the Internet generally. R. John Muller , and its affiliated companies disclaim all warranties, representations or endorsements, expressed or implied, with regard to the data, information and material included in, or accessible from, this Web site or the Internet, including, but not limited to, all implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or noninfringement. R. John Muller and its affiliated companies have the right to discontinue, change or update any data, information or material included in the Web site without prior notice, and they do not assume any legal liability or responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any data, information or material included in, or accessible from, this Web site. No advice or information given by R. John Muller or its affiliated companies shall create any warranty. Neither R. John Muller nor its affiliated companies warrants that the data, information and material included in the Web site or on the Internet will be uninterruptible or error free or that any data, information, software or other material accessible from this Web site is free of viruses or other harmful components. Several of our pages describe various insurance products. The availability of a specific product may differ from state of state. The product descriptions are general in nature and the insurance coverage’s are subject to the specific terms of the actual policies issued. If you are interested in the terms and conditions of a specific product, please contact us at 201-659-2403 for additional information.
Disclaimer of liability
In no event shall R. John Muller or its affiliated companies be liable for any compensatory, special, direct, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages, exemplary damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data, information or profits arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of the data, information or material included in this Web site or on the Internet generally or on any other basis.
Disclaimer for links
Although this site includes links providing direct access to other Internet sites, R. John Muller and its affiliated companies take no responsibility for the content or information contained on those other sites, and does not exert any editorial or other control over those other sites.
Electronic communications
R. John Muller will not be deemed to have accepted any electronic communication unless R. John Muller provides the sender of the electronic communication with an acknowledgment verifying receipt of the communication. If R. John Muller sends any electronic communication, R. John Muller will assume the communication was received intact by the intended recipient. The recipient of such message must notify R. John Muller if the transmission was not received or was not received in a readable format.
Security
Despite the security measures taken by R. John Muller, there is an inherent risk in disclosing personal information over the Internet. Anyone electronically transmitting personal information assumes the risk that such information may be disclosed or intercepted by unintended third parties and R. John Muller disclaims all liability resulting from such interception or disclosure. Anyone who wishes to apply for an insurance quote who is concerned about maintaining the security of their personal information may fax or mail the information to 930 Washington Street, Hoboken, New Jersey 07030 or Fax it to 201-659-0373.
By Jill Muratori, Esq.
© 2006 by Professional Insurance Agents. All rights reserved. 11/06
Call Us TodayWe are here for all of your insurance needs!CALL NOW: 1-201-659-2403
1-201-659-2403
info@mullerinsurance.com
PoliciesToggle NavigationFor IndividualsFor BusinessAboutToggle NavigationHomeAboutBlogContactCompaniesToggle NavigationChubbTravelersPlymouth RockThe Andover CompaniesAccreditation© Copyright
|
All Rights Reserved
|
Muller Insurance
|
Privacy Policy
Go to Top
